<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Water, Power, Network - Cities</title><link href="https://johngage.github.io/water/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://johngage.github.io/water/feeds/cities.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://johngage.github.io/water/</id><updated>2018-11-30T09:48:40-08:00</updated><subtitle>City Critical Infrastructure</subtitle><entry><title>Deep Learning</title><link href="https://johngage.github.io/water/deep-learning.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2018-11-30T09:48:40-08:00</published><updated>2018-11-30T09:48:40-08:00</updated><author><name>John Gage</name></author><id>tag:johngage.github.io,2018-11-30:/water/deep-learning.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;h3 id="jeff-dean"&gt;Jeff Dean&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;@JeffDean
ai.google/research/people/jeff&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;David Patterson, Carlos Sequin, David Culler,&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ML for robotic control&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;90 ML paper / year&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;h3 id="jeff-dean"&gt;Jeff Dean&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;@JeffDean
ai.google/research/people/jeff&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;David Patterson, Carlos Sequin, David Culler,&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ML for robotic control&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;90 ML paper / year&lt;/p&gt;</content></entry><entry><title>Berkeley Vision 2050 Commission</title><link href="https://johngage.github.io/water/berkeley-vision-2050-commission.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2018-11-28T00:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2018-11-28T00:00:00-08:00</updated><author><name>John Gage</name></author><id>tag:johngage.github.io,2018-11-28:/water/berkeley-vision-2050-commission.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;h3 id="planning-berkeley-future"&gt;Planning Berkeley Future&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last year, following the initiative by Gordon Wozniak and John Gage, Mayor Jesse Arreguín created the Berkeley 2050 Commission, ratified this November in Berkeley by the passage of Prop R.  We have four committees: Technology, Quality of Life, Financial and Management, and Environment. We plan to spend …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;h3 id="planning-berkeley-future"&gt;Planning Berkeley Future&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last year, following the initiative by Gordon Wozniak and John Gage, Mayor Jesse Arreguín created the Berkeley 2050 Commission, ratified this November in Berkeley by the passage of Prop R.  We have four committees: Technology, Quality of Life, Financial and Management, and Environment. We plan to spend 2019 in a series of exploratory meetings with all elements of the Berkeley community, culminating in a comprehensive plan for infrastructure investment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;UrbanSim would be an ideal platform, it seems, for exploration of a range of possible futures in these meetings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Berkeley will spend over $1 billion dollars in infrastructure maintenance, modification, and renovation in the next thirty years. We plan to explore the impact of new technologies on the costs of street surfacing and storm water treatment, waste water and clean water decentralization, energy system decentralization, re-engineering of all continuity systems--communications, energy distribution, water flows, transportation and materiel movement, piping systems,--and examine the costs and benefits of re-engineering all structures in Berkeley for resilience and efficiency.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Michael Reilly, Metropolitan Transportation Commission, San Francisco, California
Agile urban modelling to support regional planning in the San Francisco bay area&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bryan T. Adey, Claudio Martani, Natalia Papathanasiou, Marcel Burkhalter, ETH
Zürich
Principles for estimating and communicating the sustainability of intervention programmes
on infrastructure&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Samuel Maurer, Paul Waddell, University of California, Berkeley
Template-based task orchestration for urban modelling&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Michael Ndwiga, Richard Mulwa, Juha Siikamaki and Jessica Alvsilver, University of
Nairobi
Valuing Urban Green Spaces and Nature Restoration in a Developing Country: Application
of Choice Experiment&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Joseph Ferreira, MIT
Mi Diao, National University of Singapore
Diem Le, Xiaohu Zhang, Singapore/MIT Alliance for Research and Technology
Roberto Ponce Lopez, Jingsi Shaw, MIT
Yi Zhu, Shanghai University of Finance and Economics
P. Christopher Zegras, MIT
Integrating Accessibility Measures into the Microsimulation of Daily Real Estate Market
Dynamics&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Paul Waddell, Samuel Maurer, Geoff Boeing, University of California, Berkeley
Ignacio Garcia-Dorado, Google Research
Max Gardner, Emily Porter, University of California, Berkeley
Daniel Aliaga, Purdue University
Architecture for modular microsimulation of real estate markets and transportation&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Michael Wegener, Spiekermann &amp;amp; Wegener Urban and Regional Research (S&amp;amp;W)
Modelling Long-term Urban Change&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Keith C. Clarke, University of California, Santa Barbara
Urbanization and global change in California&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Roger White, Lien Poelmans, Karolien Vermeiren, Inge Uljee, Guy Engelen, Flemish
Institute for Technological Research
Long term simulation of urban development scenarios in support of spatial policy planning&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2016/05/18/upshot/which-buildings-in-manhattan-couldnt-be-built-again-today.html&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;http://www.quantierra.com/&lt;/p&gt;</content></entry></feed>