<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Water, Power, Network - Oceans</title><link href="https://johngage.github.io/water/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://johngage.github.io/water/feeds/oceans.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://johngage.github.io/water/</id><updated>2018-11-02T14:40:00-07:00</updated><subtitle>City Critical Infrastructure</subtitle><entry><title>Waveglider</title><link href="https://johngage.github.io/water/waveglider.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2018-11-02T14:40:00-07:00</published><updated>2018-11-02T14:40:00-07:00</updated><author><name>John Gage</name></author><id>tag:johngage.github.io,2018-11-02:/water/waveglider.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Wave Glider SV3 Wave Engine GPCTD+DO Spare Sensor (SKU Code:)
Includes a pumped Sea-Bird glider payload conductivity, temperature depth plus dissolved oxygen (GPCTD+DO) sensor with a fairing to reduce drag while it is mounted to the bottom of the sub. Software required for the Sea-Bird GPCTD+DO sensor …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Wave Glider SV3 Wave Engine GPCTD+DO Spare Sensor (SKU Code:)
Includes a pumped Sea-Bird glider payload conductivity, temperature depth plus dissolved oxygen (GPCTD+DO) sensor with a fairing to reduce drag while it is mounted to the bottom of the sub. Software required for the Sea-Bird GPCTD+DO sensor&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SV3 Fluorometry Kit (Chyl-A, Trypt, CDOM) (SKU Code:)
This sensor kit includes a pumped Turner C3 Fluorometer in a custom foam compartment that occupies 2 Modular Payload Unit (MPU) bays of the Wave Glider SV3 float. The Turner C3 is configured with Chlorophyll A, Tryptophan for Wastewater Monitoring and Chromophoric Dissolved Organic Materials (CDOM) sensors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Teledyne Workhorse Monitor 300kHz Acoustic Doppler Current Profiler (ADCP)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Liquid Robotics Wave Height Sensor (SKU Code:) Microstrain IMU, a GPS antenna and proprietary software, the sensor will provide back averaged wave heights, periods and directions&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SV3 Fluorometry Kit (Chyl-A, Phyco, Refined Fuels) (SKU Code:)
This sensor kit includes a pumped Turner C3 Fluorometer in a custom foam compartment that occupies 2 Modular Payload Unit (MPU) bays of the Wave Glider SV3 float. The Turner C3 is configured with Chlorophyll-A, Phycoerythrin (Marine Cyanobacteria) and Refined Fuels sensors.&lt;/p&gt;</content></entry></feed>